<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-05-16T13:30:56+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">RabbitJun’s Blog</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">merge &amp;amp; checkout</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/git/2024/05/16/first.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="merge &amp;amp; checkout" /><published>2024-05-16T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2024-05-16T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/git/2024/05/16/first</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/git/2024/05/16/first.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="how-to-merge-different-branches">How to Merge Different Branches</h1>
<p>Firstly, before merging, you need to commit your changes using Git. If you haven’t committed, you’ll face an error message prompting you to make a commit.</p>

<p>Secondly, once you’ve committed your changes, switch to the branch you want to integrate with another branch by typing <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">git checkout &lt;your_branch_name&gt;</code>in the terminal. This command lets you switch to the desired branch.</p>

<p>Thirdly, to merge another branch into your current branch, use the command <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">git merge &lt;branch_with_changes_you_want_to_include&gt;</code>.</p>

<p>Additionally, I encountered an error related to ownership because I was using WSL. To resolve it, I used the command <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">sudo chown -R $(whoami) &lt;path&gt;</code>.<br />
Here, sudo stands for “superuser do,” chown means “change ownership,” and -R stands for “recursive.” This command tells the computer to change the ownership of the directory recursively to the current user (whoami).</p>

<p>However, the same error occurred again, so I used a workaround: <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">git config --global add safe.directory &lt;your_path&gt;</code>. This command is not generally recommended, but I was short on time. T^T</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="git" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Merge Different Branches Firstly, before merging, you need to commit your changes using Git. If you haven’t committed, you’ll face an error message prompting you to make a commit.]]></summary></entry></feed>